plumperpass.com 2017-06-06

# Plumper Pass - The Best In BBW, Plumper, Chubby & Fat Porn

We realize that purchasing a membership requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you, our customer, that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us. This includes your name, address, phone number, email address, and credit-card information, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked to you, personally. We believe that you have a right to know, before purchasing a membership at one of our websites, exactly what information we might collect from you, why we collect it and how we use it. 

Sensational Video Inc. is the owner and operator of this website and does not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. You have the right to control your personal information as you see fit. We collect only the personal information you allow us to collect, and then it is used only to help us serve you better. 

### 1\. Personal information collected

We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using the Sensational Video Websites. This information includes your email address and a password when you register to create your membership account. We may also ask for personal information when you contact our Help Desk. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity. 

### Purchase Information

When you make a purchase using a credit card, we collect your name and your billing address for the card. We do not see or collect the card type or expiration date, and only see the last 4 digits of the card number. We collect this information in order to verify your billing address. This includes your email address and the name, address, and telephone number of the intended recipient(s). 

### 2\. Use of your personal information

Information we collect on Sensational Video Websites may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways: \- Register you as a member of Sensational Video \- Bill your credit card for your purchases \- Respond to your customer service inquiries or requests \- Communicate special bi-monthly newsletter 

### 3\. When and with whom we share your personal information

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information only with our agents, representatives and trusted service providers and contractors for the limited purposes of fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with our Websites; communicating to customers; providing customer service; enhancing and improving the customer shopping experience; Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required by law. 

### 4\. How you can control the use of your personal information

Do not share your your account password with anyone. Other than on our Websites, Sensational Video will never ask you for your password. 

### 5\. How you can decide what marketing communication you receive from us

Sensational Video may periodically send you email messages describing new items, featured merchandise and special promotions. We may also need to send operational emails to inform you of any changes to our site that might affect your personal information. 

### 6\. How we protect the security of your personal information

The security of your personal information is very important to us. In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL (and most are), your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet. Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password you created when you registered for an account (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. The confidentiality of your password is your responsibility to protect. You may change it anytime by going to "Modify Profile". Log in with your username and password, then click "Change Password" and enter a new password. 

### 7\. Changes to the Sensational Video Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this privacy policy at any time. 

### 8\. How to contact Sensational Video

If you have comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us. We will address any issue to the best of our abilities. Thank you for your support of our policies. 

### 9\. Effective Date:

The Sensational Video Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1, 2008.
